
module.exports  =[
    {
        question:"＿＿ます。",
        answer:"Write its hiragana　Kanji:合",
        rightanswer:["あい"],
    },
    {
        question:"好き",
        answer:"Writes its hiragana。Kanji:好",
        rightanswer:["す"],
    },
    {
        question:"コンサート＿さそう",
        answer:"Fill in the blank",
        rightanswer:["に"],
    },
    {
        question:"Weekday",
        answer:"Write that word in japanese。",
        rightanswer:["へいじつ","平日"],
    },
    {
        question:"pack for the trip = にもつを＿。＿。る",
        answer:"Fill in the blank。",
        rightanswer:["つめ"],
    },
    {
        question:"海外りょこう＝foreign travel",
        answer:"＿。＿。りょこう=domestic travel",
        rightanswer:["こくない","国内"],
    },
    {
        question:"行く",
        answer:"Writes its hiragana。Kanji:行",
        rightanswer:["い"],
    },
    {
        question:"分析",
        answer:"Write its hiragana",
        rightanswer:["ぶんせき"]
    },
    {
        question:"Write the word 'Play' in Japanese.",
        answer:"_。＿。＿。＿。＿。",
        rightanswer:["あそびます"],
    },
    {
        question:"足跡",
        answer:"Write its hiragana.",
        rightanswer:["あしあと"],
    },
    {
        question:"Write the word 'eldest son/first-born son' in japanese",
        answer:"＿。＿。＿。＿",
        rightanswer:["ちょうなん"],
    },
    {
        question:"宴会 = party",
        answer:"Write its hiragana",
        rightanswer:["えんかい"],
    },
    {
        question:"bank",
        answer:"Write that word in japanese　。",
        rightanswer:["銀行","ぎんごう"],
    },
    {
        question:"受付 = reception",
        answer:"Write its hiragana",
        rightanswer:["うけつけ"],
    },
    {
        question:" 物事 = things ",
        answer:"Write its hiragana.",
        rightanswer:['ものごと' ],    
    },
    {
        question:"ご飯を＿＿ます",
        answer:"Fill in the blank",
        rightanswer:['食べ' , 'たべ'],        
    },
    {
        question:"くつに石が入っています",
        answer:"Write its hiragana. Kanji: 石",
        rightanswer:["いし" ],  
    },
    {
        question:"日本で、いろいろな　経験を　しました。",
        answer:"Write its hiragana. Kanji: 経験",
        rightanswer:["けいけん"],
    },
    {
        question:"本を＿いに行く。",
        answer:"Fill in the blank",
        rightanswer:["か","買"],
    },
    {
        question:"赤ん坊",
        answer:"Write its hiragana",
        rightanswer:["あかんぼう"],
    },
    {
        question:"Floor = ＿。＿。＿。＿",
        answer:"Write that word in japanese",
        rightanswer:["じゅうたん","カーペット"],
    },

    
]